Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Sound Recordings, 2004-2005
  - Subseries I: Sound Recordings, 2004, 219 sound discs (minidiscs), 79 sound cassettes and 10 microcassettes
    - AFC 2005/015: SR382, 1 minidisc
      - Dorothy Holcomb interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR383, 1 minidisc
      - Betty Barryman interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR384, 1 minidisc
      - Scott Harwood interviewed in Farmville, Virginia, 2004-03-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR385, 1 minidisc
      - Samuel Williams, Jr., interview, 2004-03-27
    - AFC 2005/015: SR386, 1 microcassette
      - Anna Ross Harrison interviewed in Farmville, Virginia
      - Nancy Phaup interviewed in Farmville, Virginia
    - AFC 2005/015: SR387, 1 microcassette
      - Ruth Taylor interviewed in Farmville, Virginia
    - AFC 2005/015: SR388, 1 microcassette
      - Ewilda Isaac interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR389, 1 microcassette
      - Ida Mae Walton interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR390, 1 microcassette
      - Earl Townsend interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR391, 1 microcassette
      - Tony Gallegas interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR392, 1 microcassette
      - Thomas McField interview
      - Armstrong Red interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR393, 1 microcassette
      - Chris Warren interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR394, 1 microcassette
      - Anthony O. Hobbs interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR395, 1 microcassette
      - Theressa Gunnels Wesley interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR396, 1 sound cassette
      - Mary Ethel Perry interview, 2004-11-28
    - AFC 2005/015: SR397, 1 minidisc
      - Pat Harris interview
    - AFC 2005/015: SR398, 1 minidisc
      - Ray Ashmore interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
  - Subseries II: Transcripts, 2004, 34 transcripts
    MS Word .doc files also available.
    - Series III Transcription List (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Ricardo Guzmán interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-30 (Box-folder 31/2)
      Related audio
    - Hilario Romano interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-30 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Alida Montiel interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Fort McDowell, Arizona, 2004-09-02 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Gilbert Martinez interviewed by Debra Krol in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Bessie Sherrod interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - Timothy Ahrens interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Elfriede Bennett interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - Effie Jones Bowers interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - Curtis Sykes interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Ted Ohira interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25 (Box-folder 31/11)
    - Chizuko Ohira interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25 (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Ashanti Hamilton interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03 (Box-folder 31/13)
    - Willie Lovelace interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03 (Box-folder 31/14)
    - Eleanor Young Love interviewed by Rita Neubauer in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01 (Box-folder 31/15)
    - Doris Evans Russell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02 (Box-folder 31/16)
    - Guy Russell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02 (Box-folder 31/17)
    - Jack Alexander interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08 (Box-folder 31/18)
    - Gwendolyn Crimm interviewed by Rita Neubauer in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06 (Box-folder 31/19)
    - William Potter interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28 (Box-folder 31/20)
    - Leola Brown Montgomery interviewed by Vern Smith in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08 (Box-folder 31/21)
    - Walter Cates, Sr., interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28 (Box-folder 31/22)
    - Hazel Whitney interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30 (Box-folder 31/23)
    - Michael Yellow Bird interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08 (Box-folder 31/24)
    - Sister Antona Ebo interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06 (Box-folder 31/25)
    - Mary Frances Mays interviewed by Vern Smith in Hayneville, Alabama, 2004-08-16 (Box-folder 31/26)
    - William Minner interviewed by Vern Smith in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08 (Box-folder 31/27)
    - Leroy Holmes, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02 (Box-folder 31/28)
    - Anna Herron interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-06 (Box-folder 31/29)
    - Teresa Joiner interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-06 (Box-folder 31/30)
    - Rutha Mae Harris interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20 (Box-folder 31/31)
    - Nathaniel Briggs interviewed by Vern Smith in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (Box-folder 31/32)
    - Octavia Briggs interviewed by Vern Smith in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (Box-folder 31/33)
    - James Jackson interviewed by Vern Smith in Selma, Alabama, 2004-08-16 (Box-folder 31/34)
    - Roger Wilkins interviewed by Claudia Dreifus (Box-folder 31/35)
  - Subseries III: Promotional Sound Recordings, 2004-2005, 4 sound discs (CD-R)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR399, 1 CD-R
      - Interview with Wade Henderson, President of the Leadership Conference on Civil Rights
    - AFC 2005/015: SR400, 1 CD-R
      - AARP, Prime Time Radio, 2004-04-13
    - AFC 2005/015: SR401, 1 CD-R
      - AARP, Prime Time Radio, 2005-02-15
    - AFC 2005/015: SR402, 1 CD-R
      - We Walk with the Wind [song], plus additional audio
- Series IV: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Moving Images, 2004-2005
  - Subseries I: AARP, 2004, 90 videocassettes (DVCAM), 4 videocassettes (miniDV) and 3 videocassettes (VHS)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV001, 1 miniDV
      - Maureen Bunyan interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Wade Henderson interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
    - AFC 2005/015: MV002, 1 DVCAM
      - Joseph Vines, Jr., interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Unidentified interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Herbert M Jones, Sr., interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Edward Fleming interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Warren Stewart interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Hugo A. Owens interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: MV003, 1 DVCAM
      - Richard Stewart interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - James Edwards Shelfield interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Douglas Blair interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Harris Wheeler interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Ned Cary, Jr., interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - James Ashton interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Juanita Owens Wyatt interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV004, 1 DVCAM
      - Juanita Owens Wyatt interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (2 of 2)
      - Pryce Baldwin, Jr., interviewed by Nery Ynclan in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Raymond B. Whitsell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Renee King interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - William Curry interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Miscellaneous
      - Unidentified interview
    - AFC 2005/015: MV005, 1 DVCAM
      - Charles Leslie interviewed by Nery Ynclan in North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - William Howard interviewed by Nery Ynclan in North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Marjorie Edwards interviewed by Nery Ynclan in North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - James Pointer interviewed by Nery Ynclan in North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Bernice Jones interviewed by Nery Ynclan in North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Miscellaneous in North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV006, 1 DVCAM
      - Walter Johnson, Jr., interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Jacques and Shirley Overdiep interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Claudet Burroughs-White interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Charles McClennahann interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Harry Blackmon interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV007, 1 DVCAM
      - Marvin Dalton interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Ronald Francis interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Brenda Smith Harris interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Franklin McCain, Sr., interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
    - AFC 2005/015: MV008, 1 DVCAM
      - Haze Moore interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Yvonne Simmons Pettis interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Maxie Stanley Withers Granger interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV009, 1 DVCAM
      - Maxie Stanley Withers Granger interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07 (2 of 2)
      - Alex Cunningham interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Azilee Kirkland McKinght interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Lavada DeSalles interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV010, 1 DVCAM
      - Lavada DeSalles interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07 (2 of 2)
      - Unidentified interview in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - James Bland interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Frances Smith interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Naomi Stanley interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Louise Holmes interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV011, 1 DVCAM
      - James McCoy, Jr., interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - James Brane interviewed in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Johnny Ponds interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV012, 1 DVCAM
      - Albert Jabs interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Jessica Mayers interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Rosemounda Butler interviewed in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Robert Davis, Jr., interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV013, 1 DVCAM
      - Robert Davis, Jr., interviewed by Lydia Lum in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (2 of 2)
      - James Cobridge interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - John Due, Jr., interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
    - AFC 2005/015: MV014, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - China Evans interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Pamela Joyce Cooper interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Bunny Thomas interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Linda Andrews interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Charles Evans and Connie Hicks-Evans interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Oscar Crowell interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Bill Brodie interviewed in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
    - AFC 2005/015: MV015, 1 DVCAM
      - Anthony Jones interviewed by Lydia Lum in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Bob Burton interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Sarah Rudolph interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Deborah Pippin-Johnson interviewed in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Zana Ries interviewed in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
    - AFC 2005/015: MV016, 1 DVCAM
      - Leon Formby interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Herman Louis Vann interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Raymond Henry interview, 2004-08
      - Oliver Harper interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Irving Davis interview, 2004-08
      - Carolyn Givhan interviewed by Lydia Lum in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
    - AFC 2005/015: MV017, 1 DVCAM
      - Jacquelyn Coleman interviewed by Lydia Lum in Alabama, 2004-08
      - Lee Kennedy interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Alabama, 2004-08
      - Isaiah Daniel interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (1 of 2)
      - Tom Ellison interviewed in Alabama, 2004-08
      - Mitchell Halter interviewed in Alabama, 2004-08
      - Iminases Carter Friedman interviewed in Alabama, 2004-08
      - Helicopter in Alabama
    - AFC 2005/015: MV018, 1 DVCAM
      - Isaiah Daniel interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (2 of 2)
      - Geneva Thomas interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - William Garrett interviewed in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Linda White Hampton interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - AARP reporter in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Barbara Howard interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Lorene Ashley interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Sadie Gardener Penn interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
    - AFC 2005/015: MV019, 1 DVCAM
      - Francis Cobbs interview, 2004-08
      - Joanne Blackman Bland interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Naomi Rogers Randolph interviewed by Nery Ynclan, 2004-08
      - Miscellaneous
      - Emma Cornelius White interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV020, 1 DVCAM
      - James Buie interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Michael Leroy Jones interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Alyce Griffin Clarke interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Frederick Gayle, Jr., interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Walter Howell interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Percy Chapman interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Chuck Means interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
    - AFC 2005/015: MV021, 1 DVCAM
      - Ruth Weir interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - Lyvonne LeFlore interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - Kenneth Coleman interviewed in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - Gladys Ward interviewed by Lydia Lum in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
    - AFC 2005/015: MV022, 1 DVCAM
      - Bus ride in Mississippi
    - AFC 2005/015: MV023, 1 DVCAM
      - Jacob Byas interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Mississippi, 2004-08
      - Unidentified interviewed in Mississippi, 2004-08
      - Unidentified interviewed in Mississippi, 2004-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV024, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-21
    - AFC 2005/015: MV025, 1 DVCAM
      - Vida M. Gaynor interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08
      - Maynell Smith interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08
      - Doris Ginn interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08
      - Wendell P. Taylor interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV026, 1 DVCAM
      - Willis Reed, Sr., interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25 (1 of 2)
      - Richard Lewis interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
    - AFC 2005/015: MV027, 1 DVCAM
      - Clifford Boxley interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - William Ware interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV028, 1 DVCAM
      - James Hayes interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (1 of 2)
      - Carl Galmon interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Brenda Brent Williams interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Lenor Franklin and Della Foster interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Philip Baptiste interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV029, 1 DVCAM
      - Philip Baptiste interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (2 of 2)
      - Barbara Leonard interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Marie Galatas interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - David Leonard interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Frances B. Hooker interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Gail Netters interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV030, 1 DVCAM
      - Gail Netters interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (2 of 2)
      - Jacqueline Stephens interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Juanita S. Barker interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Sheila Floyd interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
    - AFC 2005/015: MV031, 1 DVCAM
      - William Ware interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25 (2 of 2)
      - Janis Scott interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Samuel Allen interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Barbara Punch interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
    - AFC 2005/015: MV032, 1 DVCAM
      - Wendell P. Taylor interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22 (2 of 2)
      - Miscellaneous in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Brenda Donnell interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Roslyn V. Anderson interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Unidentified interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Frankye Regis interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Gwendolyn Harper Owens interviewed in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
    - AFC 2005/015: MV033, 1 DVCAM
      - Kendy Owens interviewed in Mississippi, 2004-08
      - Georgia Wier interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Mississippi, 2004-08
      - James Bradford interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Mississippi, 2004-08
      - C. Lee Cody, Jr., interviewed in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV034, 1 DVCAM
      - C. Lee Cody, Jr., interviewed in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23 (2 of 2)
      - Hal Dahmer interviewed in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23
    - AFC 2005/015: MV035, 1 DVCAM
      - Tommie Jean Clark interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Dolores and Gladys Higgins interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Unidentified interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Janice Coleman Sawyer interviewed by Nery Ynclan in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Samson Skip Alexander interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Nancy Louise Jackson interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - James Hayes interviewed in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV036, 1 DVCAM
      - Johnnie A. Jones, Sr., interviewed in Louisiana, 2004-08
      - Joseph Creasy interviewed in Louisiana, 2004-08
      - Lucy M. Cohn interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Louisiana, 2004-08
      - Willis Reed, Sr., interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV037, 1 DVCAM
      - Millie J. Washington interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Scotty MacClymonds interviewed in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Meniva Williams Neamu interviewed in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV038, 1 DVCAM
      - Meniva Williams Neamu interviewed in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26 (2 of 2)
      - Bettie Patterson interviewed in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - William McGarry interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
      - Patricia Mejia interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV039, 1 DVCAM
      - Patricia Mejia interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27 (2 of 2)
      - Genaro Lopez interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27 (1 of 2)
      - Jose Cardenas interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
    - AFC 2005/015: MV040, 1 DVCAM
      - Genaro Lopez interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27 (2 of 2)
      - Ernesto Bernal interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
      - Lemma White interviewed in by Sandra Marquez in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
      - Unidentified interviewed in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
    - AFC 2005/015: MV041, 1 DVCAM
      - Regina Martinez interviewed in New Mexico, 2004-08
      - Chellis Glendinning interviewed by Lydia Lum in New Mexico, 2004-08
      - Chela Lightchild interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Mexico, 2004-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV042, 1 DVCAM
      - Tom Gonzales interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - David Romaro interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Charles Montano interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Yolanda Backtamachoi interviewed in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
    - AFC 2005/015: MV043, 1 DVCAM
      - Pablo Sedillo interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Roberto Mondragon interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
    - AFC 2005/015: MV044, 1 DVCAM
      - Alexander Weiss interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV045, 1 DVCAM
      - William Patterson interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Willie Posey interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Eugene Frazier interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV046, 1 DVCAM
      - Eugene Frazier interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (2 of 2)
      - Charles Aikens interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Ernestine Marshall interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
    - AFC 2005/015: MV047, 1 DVCAM
      - Children in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Rondia White interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Bobby Lee interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Marilyn Anderson interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - James Finley interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV048, 1 DVCAM
      - James Finley interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05 (2 of 3)
      - Carol Ruth Silver interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (1 of 2)
      - James Lewis interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV049, 1 DVCAM
      - Delores Richard interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Norva Bell interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05